In the last lecture we added this toggle button and it works fine,
Eklediimiz Son Ders sadece dmeyi deitirip iyi alyor.
let's now make sure that we actually turn this into something more pretty.
Bunu daha ok ho bir eye dntrdmzden emin olalm.
For that, I'll add a css file to my drawerToggle component,
Unutmayn, Eddas bizi ekmecene d olarak gryor, bileen tablasn konuuyoruz.
drawerToggle.css and in there, I want to style this as a hamburger icon. Now attached to this video, you
CSS ile konumak CSS ve orada bir hamburger olarak stil istiyorum imdi bu videoyu
will find the css code which is responsible for that and this code essentially just creates a div
ekleyebilirsiniz, bunun iin sorumlu olan CSS kodunu bulacaksnz ve bu kod aslnda yalnzca iinde
with three bars inside of it where each bar is one of the hamburger icon bars.
ubuk bulunan bir div oluturuyor burada her ubuk Barnabileceim bir kulbeden biridir.
Now to make that css code work, we need to adjust the actual html or jsx code,
imdi C'yi asl olarak HDMI ya da J ayarna ihtiya duyduumuz gibi yapyor musunuz? X kodu var.
so there we no longer have a div which wraps the menu text
Yani artk men metnini saran bir div yok.
instead what we'll have is a div which holds three div elements inside of it.
Bunun yerine bunun iinde zgr def elemanlar barndran bir div var.
And these div elements don't have any content,
Bu gelimelerin ierii de yok.
don't have any css class due to the assigned styling
Atanan stil yznden ABD snf olarak C'ye sahip olmayn.
they will be styled correctly because I'm styling all divs which are nested in a div or in any element
Bir div iinde i ie gemi tm div'leri veya tabii ki her bir ekmeceyi d div iin snfa doru atamak
which has the drawerToggle class. That of course means we have to assign this drawerToggle class
zorunda olduumuz anlamna gelen snf izmek veya boyu yklemek zorunda olan herhangi bir eye stil koyduumuz iin
to the outer div.
bunlar doru ekilde biimlendirilirler.
So i'll import classes from the css file to get access to that class and then add class name to the outer
Asfalttaki tm import maddeleri bu snfa eriebilir ve sonra da snf d div'a ekleyip snflar atayabilir veya
div and assign classes drawerToggle referring to that drawerToggle css class which is set up there.
bu karaktere atfta bulunarak gei yapabilir, C'yi orada kuran snf olarak deitirir.
So make sure all files are saved
Bylece tm dosyalarn kaydedildiinden emin olun.
and let's then have a look at that,
Ve sonra bir gz atalm.
and here we see the nice looking hamburger icon. And with it we get a pretty nice looking application
Ve burada grdmz ho grnml hamberger' gryoruz ve onunla birlikte, kendi burgerimizi
where we can build our own burger, check it out, continue
ina etmenin devam edebileceini gzelce gzel bir uygulama gryoruz.
which doesn't do too much yet and have a lot of nice looking functionality in there.
Hangisi ok fazla ey yapmyor ve ok gzel grnml ilevsellik ieriyor.
Now over the next modules, we'll add more functionality like sending this or the data to a real server, adding
gerek bir sunucuya birden fazla sayfa eklemek ve uygulama durumunu farkl ekilde ele almak gibi
multiple pages and handling the application state differently but I'm already pretty happy with this
daha fazla ilevsellik ekleyeceiz, ancak uygulamadaki bu durumdan memnuniyet duyuyorum ve imdi unu
state of the application and I'd say let's now have a look at how we may optimize this or what we can
syleyelim: Bunu nasl optimize edebileceimizi veya kayt modlleri iin ilerlemeden nce bununla ilgili neler bulabileceimizi inceleyin.
fine tune about that before we move on with other course modules.
Artk bir sonraki modl zerinde, DS veya veri gndermek